## **ANGELA NYABUTI**

P.O BOX 358-40502 | +254 (0) 712 688 425 | nyabutiangella@gmail.com | https://github.com/angelanyabuti

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a detail-oriented software engineer with a degree in Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. I have experience in developing mobile applications and web applications and working with frameworks such as bootstrap, Laravel and codeigniter. I am proficient with the following languages: JavaScript, PHP, SQL and C#.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### VORTEX SOLUTIONS LIMITED

Westlands, Nairobi

# **Software Engineer Officer**

February 2023 – Current

- Developing software solutions by studying information needs and conferring with users.
- Documenting and demonstrating solutions by developing documentations.
- Implementing ERP and POS systems.
- Configuring and intergrating client's mobile payment system with their POS system.
- Troubleshooting installed systems for any malfunctions, errors and advising the organization. and the clients on the best course of action.

#### **VORTEX SOLUTIONS LIMITED**

Westlands, Nairobi May 2022 – August 2022

## **Software Engineer Intern**

- Accompanied technicians to client visits
- Assisted in implementation of ERP and POS systems
- Trained in till configuration
- Trained in server configuration
- Worked alongside other technicians to build an android application for a client

#### **EDUCATION**

#### THE CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF EASTERN AFRICA

Nairobi, Kenya

• Bachelor of Science in Computer Science.

May 2019 – October 2023

## TENGECHA GIRLS HIGH SCHOOL

Kericho

• Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

February 2015 – November 2018

#### ST. PETERS' GIRLS BOARDING SCHOOL

**Elburgon** 

• Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

January 2010 – November 2014

#### **ADDITIONAL**

**Technical Skills**: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, PHP and C#.

Commercial Skills: Teamwork skills, Problem solving and logical thinking skills, Strong

creative ability, Computer literacy, GitHub.

# **ANGELA NYABUTI**

P.O BOX 358-40502 | +254 (0) 712 688 425 | nyabutiangella@gmail.com | https://github.com/angelanyabuti

### **REFEREES**

Mr. Alfred Omondi, Systems Architect, Vortex Solutions Limited, P.O BOX 17907-00100, 0742750872. alfredsolomon35@gmail.com

Mr. Geoffrey Twabe, Software installation and Deployment Technician, Vortex Solutions Limited, P.O BOX 17907-00100, 0735001352. twabe.g@vortexsol.com

### Lecturer,

Mr. Vincent Kibet, The Catholic University of Eastern Africa, P.O BOX 62157-00200, 0712 728 062.